{
    "id": "1e547e36e4ac42718f8cb7ecfd0311dd",
    "title": "Omission Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Take the book with you in case you will see Mary.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "in case",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "986a77148910418eb7ada42c539819d1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Thatâ€™s the house where he was born in.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "was",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fac4a2661b8b4e0a8a0529d0a8a5d535"
        },
        {
            "question": "She had died a couple of years ago.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "had",
                "a",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f064ea67cad048f3ba40b302bbf224ce"
        },
        {
            "question": "He asked that what I was doing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "33b6b82611ee4fdfb40fe7a453a988b8"
        },
        {
            "question": "He asked to her why she was angry.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "why",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1fa7788717144725883e61e94e071e09"
        },
        {
            "question": "When I will go to Mexico, I will see him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "to",
                "when"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "463d844b0d21415e83cc2069720c4aee"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is very much angry.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "very",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "42dbb14be0344da18343143576a77280"
        },
        {
            "question": "Yesterday in the evening he came to dinner.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in the",
                "came",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3499244a8eec4e4f8af445f3c9213b32"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is my friend who he was at school with me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "he",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e241a321c4ff4b9e95bd780c6fd30816"
        },
        {
            "question": "Supposing if you fail, what will you do?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "fail",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2a71d89573014f72aa85d8014ba5ce7f"
        }
    ]
}